(new wave music)
♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Way down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank ♪
♪ Were hatching an evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular Joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment
needed a good test case ♪
♪ So they conked
him on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot him into space ♪
- [Mike] Let me go!
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
♪ Tom Servo ♪
♪ Croooow ♪
♪ If you're wonderin' how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(spaceship ambience)
(doors closing)
- Whoa whoa, hold it
right there, fella
come back here and
sign in, please.
- Hey, hey, what's up, Servo.
- All right, company policy.
- What, sense when?
- Well since things
have been gettin'
too darn lax around here,
you realize just about
anybody could walk up here
on The Satellite of Love here,
wanderin' around?
- Well, I live here.
- You can't expect me to
keep track of every face.
- Hey, let me just drop these
Molemen comics off with
Crow, I'll be right back.
- Now hold on a second.
(beep)
Hello, Crow.
- [Crow] What?
- We got a uh, what's
the name again?
- Mike Nelson.
- We got a Mike Nelson up here,
you expectin' him down there
on that side of the ship?
- [Crow] Nelson, yeah, yeah.
- Huh, well, sign in please.
- (laughing) Sign
in too, all right.
- Don't forget the time.
- Uh huh, and that's?
- 11:43
- 11:43.
Okay, I'll just drop these off.
Be right back.
Crow, here you go.
All right.
- Whoa-ho-ho-ho,
sign out, will ya!
- Oh, come on,
this is ridiculous!
- Company policy!
- We'll be right back.
- 11:43, wait, 11:44.
- 11:44.
(new wave music)
(snoring loudly)
- I think we'd
better wake him up.
He did a couple of
back-to-back shifts.
Servo!
- Ahhh!
- Ah!
- Red alert! Red
alert! Send back up!
Someone's breaking into
the vending machine!
- And to think he's
gettin' $4.35 an hour.
- Yeah, ah, Ponch
and John are calling.
♪ Clay looks better in a
sweater washed in (trails off) ♪
- Let's see, put the white
cottons in with the denim.
Where is that silk dress anyway?
Put the towels in with the
woolens and what's this here?
Ugh.
- Huh, what?
Oh, Nelson, come on in,
laundry day down here.
Once a year whether there's a
full load or not. (laughing)
Where was I?
Oh yes.
Have you noticed that coffee
houses are all the rage?
Well, I've observed
that coffee houses
are bursting at the seams
with pretentiousness.
Therefore, you can't
even be in a coffee house
and not be pretentious.
Now to prove it to you, the
unbeliever, I've sent along up
some of the trappings
of the coffee house,
surly waitress not included.
- Clay, where are
your fine washables?
I know I bought you more
underpants than we have here.
Give me that.
- Oh come on, I think we
can be in a coffee house
without becoming pretentious.
- Sure, don't worry, Mike.
We'll just sit here
and prove him wrong.
- I don't feel a thing.
- Yeah, it's
definitely not working.
- Nope.
(sniffing)
- I've been recording my
life in pastels. (laughing)
- The only question
worth asking is,
"What am I going
through right now?"
- You, the white male,
are my personal oppressor.
Oh my.
- Yes, yes, she is so great.
- Mm hmm.
- I saw her one woman show,
her soul cried out to me.
- So I'll take my
rage and box it up!
And take it out with the trash!
- Yes, yes.
- Oh fantastic.
- Thanks a lot, Dr. Forrester,
see what you've done?
You've turned my robots into
self-absorbed little poseurs.
- A white male
middle-class power holder
would say that, Mike.
- I'm not a white ma--
- Fascist!
- Tell 'em, sister!
- (groaning) Ah, oh hoo
hoo-hoo, a-booga-booga-ha!
Hahaha, oh, pardon my revelry,
but I prove once again that
Dr. Clayton Forrester is
right right right, hahaha.
Well, your movie
this week, Cowsills,
is called "The Creeping Terror".
and I just know you'll
hate it. (giggling)
Thank you. (laughing)
- Hey, I'll show you
creeping terrors.
These grass stains.
- Well, don't you get it, Mike?
The fact that we can acknowledge
our own pretentiousness
says something
about us as artists.
- But we're not artists.
- Well, maybe your not, Mike
(laughing condescendingly)
- Well, I don't
think any of us--
(alarm buzzing)
- Oh, we got movie sign!
- [Crow] Oh this thing,
yes, I suppose I'll run.
(spaceship ambience)
(doors opening)
(ominous music)
- [Servo] Oh and now this.
- [Mike] Hey, don't start it.
Oh, who put hair in the sink?
- [Crow] That was me.
- [Servo] The things I
can do with my Spirograph.
- [Crow] When spiders
drink too much.
- [Servo] I'm getting ready
to get so scared. (laughs)
- [Mike] These people
saved with MCI.
- [Servo] Wow.
- [Crow] Ah, this
is nothing a good
wide tooth comb
couldn't take care of.
- [Mike] First transatlantic
cable got all screwed up.
- [Servo] You know,
maybe this is a doorway
to another dimension,
not one of sight and
of sound, but of mind.
Nah.
- [Crow] Looks like the inside
of Robert Morley's nose.
- [Mike] See, this
is all I ever see
when I look into a microscope.
- [Servo] Guys, I tell ya,
I wanna be filled with
suspense, but uh (trails off)
- [Crow] Tonight
at the Metrodome,
monster designed by John Lackey
(making guttural noises).
- [Mike] Gogo the Gorilla.
(Servo singing
rhythmically to music)
- [Mike] Oh no, Kopp.
(intense staccato music)
- [Servo] Ya know, a
steady diet of staccato
is a bit nauseating.
- [Crow] Don't
forget the Phillips.
- [Servo] A. J., a jerk.
(laughing stupidly)
- [Crow] The point of
view of Helen Keller.
- [Mike] Why it's not creeping,
this Terror is clipping
along just fine.
- [Servo] A very uninvolving
video game, this.
- [Mike] Oof, I get car
sick when I'm not in front.
- [Crow] Darkness at the
edge of town hall over town.
- [Servo] (yawning)
Boy, am I terrified.
- You must be dead, honey,
after drivin' all night.
What time is it?
- [Mike] Time for you
to get a breath mint.
- Almost 4:30.
Almost dawn.
- [Crow] Wake up, little Susy.
We should be home
in another hour.
- [Narrator] This man's
name is Martin Gordon.
- [Servo] He'll be
home in an hour.
- [Narrator] Lovely girl
beside him is Brett,
his Bride of two
wonderful weeks.
- [Mike] They have
everything, I have nothing!
- [Narrator] It was August.
They're returning from their
honeymoon to their home
in quiet, peaceful,
Angel County, California.
- [Crow] Yes, they
did the nasty.
- [Narrator] Martin's uncle
Ben is sheriff of Angel County
and Martin is his senior deputy.
- [Servo] Oh, I'm impressed.
- [Narrator] Martin has high
hopes of succeeding his uncle
when Ben retires.
- [Mike] Creeping nepotism.
- [Narrator] But for now,
Martin has only the thoughts,
emotions, and pride
of a very happy,
newly married young man.
- [Crow] He told me so.
- [Narrator] Brett is his
and he feels no man
could ask for more.
(high pitched sound)
Now without warning,
their honeymoon is to
become a nightmare.
- [Servo] Her mother showed up!
(all laughing)
- [Crow] Shortly here,
the nightmare will begin.
- [Servo] Pretty soon now.
- [Mike] Nightmare time.
Oh Martin!
- [Servo] Ignition was
a little early, but--
- [Narrator] Neither
Martin nor Brett
saw the glowing rocket descend
in the early morning sky.
It was reported to the
sherriff's office by Jeff,
the county forest ranger.
Jeff reported to Sheriff
Ben that a plane had crashed
near Willow Creek, that he
was going out to investigate.
- [Crow] Bob Dole!
- And said he would join him
as soon as possible.
Barney, Ben's junior deputy,
was to summon medical aid
and to see if he could rouse
someone at the Air Authority
in San Francisco.
- [Servo] Barney
smoked in the garage,
and look what happened.
(sloppy brass instrumentation)
- [Servo] Meanwhile, the
bride made her first meal.
(all laughing)
- [Servo] Oh you.
- [Crow] Is the band tuning up?
- [Servo] Now that we need
a narrator he clams up.
What's goin' on?
- [Mike] Looks like
Queen Latifah's hat.
- [Servo] I think a
Wal-Mart has landed.
- [Crow] Oh god, it's
Far-Out Space Nuts.
- [Mike] Astro-Nuts
(Servo imitating music)
Oh, it's gonna eliminate!
- [Servo] Oh look,
the spaceship is cute,
oo the little nose.
- [Crow] While we're
waiting, I might point out
that Angel County has
great opportunities
for light industrial
development,
Local schools...
(Servo laughing)
- [Mike] Chinese
funeral procession.
- [Servo] What?
He's from Planet Dreadloc.
- [Crow] The
pontiff has arrived.
- [Mike] I was afraid the
alien was gonna be goofy.
- [Servo] Oo, man, it's bright,
should have brought
my Ray Bans, wow!
(monster screeching)
(Servo imitating noise)
- [Crow] Ah, thank you,
thank you very much,
thank you, haha!
- [Mike] Ohayo, ohayo,
those I must, ohayo.
- [Servo] And don't come back.
- [Crow] Oh, I forgot my purse.
- [Mike] Jeez, it's
aerodynamically perfect.
- [Servo] Oh boy, my
back is killin' me.
I came to this planet 'cause
I heard they have Doans pills.
- [Crow] He's tryin'
to carry off a look
and he's just not
tall enough for it.
- [Mike] Sneak in back
of this bush here.
(police siren)
- [Servo] Indiana wants me.
- It's Uncle Ben, honey.
Must be an accident
or something.
- [Mike] Yee-haw!
- [Crow] Honey not here.
- [Servo] Boy, you
newlyweds are randy.
Now stop it in there!
- There's a plane crash down
the road a couple of miles.
I'm gonna be a little
shorthand 'til help gets here.
Pull around back of me.
- [Mike] Go on about
your marriage, nothin'
happenin' here.
(snare drum march)
(Servo imitating music)
- [Servo] This is
the army, Mr. Jones.
- Come along, both of you.
- [Crow] Annette
Funicello wore khakis.
- Get in, honey.
- [Mike] You have the
right to remain mine.
- [Servo] Okay, now get
out, honey. (laughing)
- [Mike] So anyway, we
didn't see much of the Dells.
But we saw the House on
the Rock, which was neat.
(monster screeching)
(Servo imitating monster)
- [Crow] Ha, still goin'.
- [Servo] Well it is creeping,
you've gotta give it that.
- [Mike] Well, it turns
out the creeping terror
likes to frolic in
the field. (giggles)
- [Servo] Lollygagging.
- [Crow] I think he's
attracted to that foliage.
- [Servo] Power walking
just isn't his thing.
- [Mike] Hey, if it landed
right in Sunset Strip,
he wouldn't be out of
place, am I right here?
(all laughing)
- [Crow] I think he's
self-conscious about
his big ol' butt.
- [Servo] Well anyway,
I like being married,
although I do wish he'd go
home at some point. (giggling)
- [Crow] Would you
two stop makin' out,
we've got an
investigation to do!
- [Narrator] At the
location of the crash,
they discovered Jeff's truck,
but Jeff himself was not around.
They proceeded with
their investigation.
- [Mike] Oh, I'm the narrator.
I was just on break,
I hope you don't mind.
- [Servo] Yep, it's
a truck all right.
It's in park, I'll
put that in my report.
- [Mike] Well, county government
was just getting
organized at this point.
- [Crow] Well, I
don't understand it
so let's start shootin'.
- [Narrator] They looked at
the rocket in utter amazement.
- [Servo] It looks like
a Ticonderoga number two.
- [Narrator] A puzzled
Ben finally asked Martin
what he made of the crash.
- [Mike] Martin
panicked and froze.
- It's no airplane.
- [Crow] Ben never asked
Martin another question.
- Could be one of our missiles.
- [Servo] This county
has missiles, sir?
- Or one of theirs.
- [Mike] Shh, honey, no.
- You could be right, honey.
I don't think we have
anything this big.
- [Mike] I know that
from our wedding night.
(all laughing)
- [Crow] Well, whatever it is,
it appears to have lowered
their intelligence level!
- [Servo] You know, if I
could find a windshield,
I'd give it a ticket. (laughs)
Sheriff.
- [Mike] Where's that one guy,
the, whatcha call
it, narrator guy?
Hey, buddy!
- [Narrator] Ben
could not understand
why the craft wasn't
severely damaged.
- [Crow] He started crying.
(Servo and Crow gasp)
- [Servo] Wait, I've been here.
I'm dead!
- [Mike] Apparently Dan
Blocker had been there.
- [Servo] What kind of a
man-beast would wear this?
- This hat belongs
to Jeff Peters.
- [Mike] Oh, it's
Jeff Peters' rocket.
- Jeff!
Jeff, Jeff are ya in there?
- [Crow] Uh, yeah,
uh, can it wait?
- Martin, go back to my
car and get my flashlight.
- [Servo] I'll just
pout. (whimpering)
(new wave music)
(Servo panting)
- [Mike] So you pretty
serious about your husband?
Uh, no, you're--
- [Servo] Guh, what's
my time? (panting)
- Ben, don't go in there.
You don't know what's in there.
- [Mike] Go, go, go, go, go.
- [Crow] Go.
- I think I hear
it moving inside.
Maybe he's hurt.
- [Servo] I gotta
check under the movie.
Oh yeah, this is a big
mess under here, jeez.
- Ben, please don't.
- [Crow] Go.
(monster screeching)
- [Servo] Oo.
(explosion)
- [Crow] (laughs) That old
gag, exploding flashlight!
- Ben.
(monster screeching)
- [Mike] He almost
showed an emotion there.
- [Servo] Honey, we gotta go
open the gifts at mom's house.
(Brett screaming)
(monster screeching)
(Ben screaming)
- [Servo] Doesn't sound good.
(monster screeching)
(Ben screaming)
- [Mike] Well, he probably
knows what he's doing. (laughs)
- [Servo] This is the
worst honeymoon I've ever,
oh, it's my first
honeymoon! (laughs)
- [Crow] I know he'd want us
to take the sheriff's car.
- Car one, calling in.
- [Mike] Reporting
large steering wheel.
- Car one, calling in.
- [Servo] I have some bad
news and some bad news.
(snare drum)
- [Crow] Here comes the Rocori
Sauk Rapids High School Band!
- [Narrator] Within the hour,
Martin's unusual
call for assistance
was answered by a special unit
led by a Colonel James Caldwell.
- [Servo] We're the
special unit, hello!
(Crow laughing)
- [Mike] It took about an hour.
They stopped at
Hardee's on the way.
(snare drum)
(Servo imitating trumpet)
- [Colonel] Let's get going.
- [Crow] There is a branch.
This is not a drill.
- [Colonel] Let's go,
let's go, move it over.
Let's get going.
- [Servo] Ah, yes, the days
of rampant military spending.
- [Colonel] All right, back
on the truck, let's go.
- [Mike] We push more
logs before 9:00 a.m.
than most people do all day!
(snare drum and piano)
- [Crow] They popped
a little Dave Brubeck
into the tape deck.
- [Servo] Just by
moving that tree,
an owl has lost its habitat.
(snare drum and piano)
- [Mike] Rose said
Sharon's havin' a baby!
(trumpet fanfare)
(Servo imitating trumpet)
- [Crow] Aw, somebody
took our campsite.
- [Servo] Okay, guys,
don't frag me again.
- [Colonel] Sergeant, take
one man and check it out.
- Yes, sir.
- [Crow] 'Cause we're special!
- Okay.
- [Mike] Uh, should we go?
I think he wants us to go.
- [Servo] (whimpering)
I'm a-scared.
- [Crow] I'll go first.
After he's done eating
me, Joe, you go in.
Sooner or later,
indigestion will set in.
- [Mike] More troops are
sent in to fix the manifold.
(Crow chewing and slurping)
- [Servo] Ah, the
original concept
for the Iwo Jima sculpture.
(electronic frequency
and beeping)
- [Mike] They're
gonna force earthlings
to read their gas meters!
(Crow gasps)
(machinery beeping)
(Servo beeping)
- [Crow] Aw great, a race
of ham radio operators.
- [Servo] Yes, this
can all be yours!
(machinery beeping)
(Servo beeping)
- [Mike] Well, they've
perfected the dial.
- [Crow] Are we inside
Television City?
- [Servo] And back again
in case we missed anything.
- [Mike] The prices
on these Kenwoods!
The aliens must be insane!
(monster roaring)
- [Servo] (gasps) It's
conglomerate rock!
- [Mike] Oh please, just
five more minutes, Mom.
(purposeful music)
- [Crow] If there's a whole
bunch of dials in there,
I'll be so jealous.
- [Servo] There's the aliens,
shoot 'em! (imitating gunfire)
- [Narrator] The
sergeant reported seeing
an amazingly large creature
in the aft section
of the strange craft.
- [Mike] He thought
it was Boog Powell.
- [Narrator] Further
reported that it was secured
by a kind of metal harness,
but that the creature could
still move around somewhat,
and for that reason, they had
not gotten too close to it.
- [Crow] Plus, they're yeller.
- [Narrator] No trace
of either Ben or Jeff
- [Servo] Or Akbar.
- [Narrator] The colonel
ordered continuous guard duty
around the spaceship
and decided to set up a
temporary military headquarters
at the sheriff's office in town.
- [Mike] It was a brilliant
strategic maneuver.
- [Crow] Yes, sir.
Jagoff.
- [Servo] Back at the high
school, shop class was canceled.
- [Narrator] By the next day,
Colonel Caldwell had the
situation well in hand.
- [Mike] K.D. Lang!
- [Narrator] He had
called Washington
and received his orders from
the highest possible authority.
- [Servo] God.
- [Narrator] He was to
maintain tight security
and to await the arrival
of a Dr. Bradford,
who had been on assignment
at the Jodrell Bank Radio
Observatory in England.
Upon arrival, Bradford was
to take complete charge
of the operation.
- [Crow] Constant craving.
- [Narrator] He was the
world's leading authority
on space emissions.
- Yuck.
- Eeugh.
He had worked out
a series of systems
that might lead to communication
with other forms of life.
When, as, and if
they were contacted.
- [Mike] Preposition city!
- [Narrator] Martin was outraged
by the government's
intellectual approach
to a monster that
had already killed
and caused the disappearance
of his two close friends.
- [Servo] Not since the
Lincoln-Douglas debate.
- [Narrator] Caldwell
tended to agree with him,
but stated he had to
follow his orders.
- [Crow] It was a real
interesting conversation.
- [Narrator] One of those orders
was to suppress the news of
the death of Ben and Jeff.
Martin was appointed
temporary sheriff
and all news intended
for public consumption
was to emanate from his office.
- [Servo] What's
emanate mean, sir?
- [Narrator] The Air Authority
issued a coverup story
that a plane had
crashed and burned,
and this was to suffice
until the experts
cleared up the mystery
of the visitor from outer space.
- [Mike] Then they went on to
plot the Bay of Pigs Invasion.
- [Crow] Hey,
welcome to the show.
- [Narrator] In a remote
section of the county,
the first of a series
of tragedies took place.
- [Servo] Two ladies!
- [Narrator] Tragedies that
would have been avoided
had the public been warned.
(monster roaring)
- [Mike] Is she really
going out with him?
- [Crow] Oh great, the
monster's a voyeur.
- [Servo] You know,
this is how all
teenagers see themselves.
Poor kids.
- [Mike] The unbearable
whiteness of being.
(Servo laughing)
- [Crow] I'll be
there in about an hour
if you can just bear with me.
- [Servo] (moaning)
Oh, Jerry, you wild animal!
(monster roaring)
Eh, eh, huh?
- [Mike] Oh my God, it's my dad!
- [Crow] We have to
get out of here, honey.
We only have an hour to eat,
have sex, and then leave.
(monster roaring)
- [Mike] Uh, come on, honey.
Let's crab walk outta here.
(woman screaming)
(monster roaring)
- [Servo] Could you at least
not eat my bathing suit,
it's brand new.
(woman screaming)
(monster roaring)
- [Mike] You have a kind face.
- [Crow] You're lucky
you have thick hair!
(woman screaming)
(monster roaring)
- [Servo] Well, he's not shy,
you can say that much about him.
(Crow and Mike laughing)
- [Mike] Hey, if you could
help me out by climbin' in...
(Crow and Servo laughing)
- [Crow] 'Twas
beauty fed the beast.
- [Servo] Wow!
(monster screaming)
Always fun to cook for,
'cause he enjoys eating!
(monster screaming)
- [Mike] Oh, the legs are
always the last to go.
- [Servo] Mm hm.
- [Crow] Would you eat
like a human being, please?
This is so rude!
- [Servo] Ah, needs
some seasoning!
- [Mike] Last time
I eat Norwegian.
(woman screaming)
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] Earth girls
are greazy. (laughs)
- [Mike] Oh wait, it's
Lent, I swore off girls!
Oh well.
- [Crow] I can't believe
I ate the whole thing.
- [Servo] You ate it, Ralph.
Good goin' down but, oh,
then they just sit there.
(spaceship beeping)
- [Mike] I love you, spaceship.
(all yell in surprise)
- [Servo] Wow.
- [Mike] It's the
creeping newlywed.
- [Crow] I have no
idea what I'm doing.
- [Servo] All you dials
and gauges, I'm in charge.
- [Mike] At this point,
the director attempted
an arty sort of shot.
(Servo laughing)
- [Crow] That other monster
must be the opener for this one.
- [Mike] Oh yeah.
- [Servo] Danger,
danger, Will Robinson!
(monster roaring)
(spaceship ambience)
(doors closing)
- Oh Mike, you know
that California flag?
The one with the
goofy looking' bear?
- California grizzly bear.
They're extinct, you know.
- Oh, too bad.
Anyway, I was thinkin',
we are many and yet we are one
here on the Satellite of
Love, just like California.
And so I made us a flag!
And Mike?
- Yes?
- Hut ti tup!
- Mike, would you
help us raise it?
- Yes.
(laughing)
Okay.
(Servo imitating snare drum)
- I pledge allegiance
to the flag
of the Satellite of Love,
free, united, glorious, fruited,
that grand bi-lobed orb,
born of the loins
of our founder,
Jacques du Bourgoin
One Eye Canapadidiwa,
farmer, claims adjuster, rebel
with alabaster symmetry and
golden grains of Xanadu!
One satellite under God, or not,
indirigible, with liberty
and justice for all.
Thank you.
(pop gun pops)
Oh, one last thing, Michael.
Check your nightstand.
You'll find a cyanide capsule
in case we're ever taken.
- I'm not taking cyanide.
- Aren't you one of us, Mike?
- Well, cyanide goes
to my hips. (laughs)
- A Tory, eh!
Outsider!
Revenges!
Provocateur!
- We'll be right back.
- Do you not know
that you have only one
live to live as a plant?
Give me liberty or kill me!
- [Crow] Hm?
- [Servo] Hey, my hat.
- [Mike] I'm not, no,
no, I'm not going.
- [Crow] Red, commie.
- [Narrator] While they
were awaiting the arrival
of Dr. Bradford, Martin
instructed Barney,
on advice from Colonel Caldwell
to plant in the
local papers the news
that Ben and Jeff had
taken off on a fishing trip
to British Columbia.
The Colonel had impressed
the bereaved families
with the necessity of
maintaining secrecy,
and these brave
relatives had agreed.
- [Mike] After being beaten.
- [Servo] Oo.
So, should we have at it
again, honey? (laughs)
- [Crow] Well, I think you're
a wonderful acting sheriff.
- [Narrator] Despite
Brett's inquiries
about what Martin had
seen in the spacecraft,
he avoided specific details
for fear of disturbing
her more than she was.
- [Servo] What's she doing?
- [Narrator] If the
truth were known,
Martin was more than a
little disturbed himself.
- [Mike] Now cough, honey.
- [Narrator] Shortly thereafter,
Dr. Bradford arrived.
- [Crow] I said Dr.
Bradford arrived.
- [Narrator] He was
a much younger man
than one would imagine.
- [Servo] I have
no preconceptions.
- Martin, I'd like for
you to meet Dr. Bradford.
- I've heard a lot about
you from the Colonel.
- Well, nothing bad, I trust.
- [Mike] Handsome, aren't I?
- Martin and his wife
were in the original party
that found the fallen craft.
(Crow laughing)
- I was sorry to hear
about your uncle.
Tough break.
- [Servo] Which one
of us is talking?
- I hope you're feeling better.
- Yes, thank you.
A couple hours of sleep
did a world of good.
- Bradford thanks the
colonel for his assistance,
and then asks to
speak to Martin.
- [Servo] Martin, have you
noticed how young I look?
- [Narrator] Bradford
questioned Martin
about everything
that had transpired.
- [Mike] Well, we
met and got married.
- [Narrator] To recall
everything in precise detail.
(Servo imitating slap bass)
- [Narrator] Really
didn't have much for him.
The two soldiers that
entered the rocket earlier
had been summoned
and Bradford hoped to
learn more from them.
- [Crow] You know, I'm
only 35. (chuckles)
- [Narrator] Would
not enter the rocket
until the arrival of
certain equipment.
- [Servo] And
fresh under things.
- [Narrator] From his
discussion, it was apparent
that the doctor
considered this situation
a magnificent
opportunity for mankind.
- [Mike] He celebrated
with a Chesterfield.
- [Narrator] He felt that
if he could communicate
with the creature,
it might be possible to advance
human knowledge by years
or even centuries.
- [Crow] Or maybe
just a few days.
- [Narrator] The spaceship alone
signified an
intellectual development
far in advance of
anything on earth.
- [Servo] Especially these two.
- [Narrator] When
Martin asked him
how he intended to protect
himself from the creature,
Bradford said not to worry.
- [Crow] Then he slapped him.
- [Narrator] He hadn't
come here to be victimized
either by his own or
the creatures feared.
- [Mike] Go ahead, punch
me in the stomach, come on!
- [Servo] Oh, it's so
fulfilling being married.
- [Mike] There, our one plate.
- [Crow] Oh, Martin invited
the alien home for supper
without telling his wife!
- [Servo] D'oh!
- [Mike] Martin keeps a
softball glove above the stove.
- [Servo] Okay, now it's not
gonna look like meatloaf,
but it is.
She boils it, I don't know why.
Ew.
Eh, just eat.
- [Crow] Oh, she's getting
the breakfast dishes done
just in time.
- [Mike] Hi, honey.
Pregnant yet?
- [Servo] I'm pretty
sure this is my house.
I haven't lived here that long.
Why don't you go in
and check it out?
- [Crow] You grab the stereo,
I'll get the silverware.
- [Mike] Shh, give
me the chloroform.
- [Servo] Ah, the Menendez
brothers come home. (laughs)
- [Crow] It's nice
how they're so playful
after the day's
murder and mayhem.
- [Servo] I hope she comes
out and blows 'em away.
(chuckles)
- [Mike] Love how you
put the medicine cabinet
in the living room.
(easy listening music)
- [Servo] Woo. (imitating drums)
- [Crow] Operation mild
surprise is going really good.
- [Servo] Boy, when law
enforcement gets playful, huh?
(laughing)
- [Mike] Oh, hi honey.
(Brett gasps)
- [Servo] Boy, three days
and it's still like
they're just newlyweds.
- [Crow] The deputy and
his siren! (chuckling)
- [Mike] Officer third wheel.
- [Servo] Aw.
Wow, what happens when she
cooks well? (rolls tongue)
(clears throat)
- [Crow] I could use a lozenge!
- [Mike] Did you bring home
your longtime companion?
- Oh, hi, Barney.
We'll be right out.
- [Barney] Oh, that's all right.
Just take your time.
- [Crow] I won't
listen or anything.
- I didn't know we had company.
Look at me, I'm a mess!
- [Servo] She's saucier
than this town deserves.
(rolls tongue)
- Don't be impolite.
Make our guest a drink.
- [Mike] Martin's
lipstick was smudged.
- Now you're talkin', honey.
What'll you have Barney?
- [Crow] Your wife!
I, oh, shoot!
How 'bout a bourbon and seven?
- Comin' up.
Would you get the seven, honey?
- [Servo] Heh, I'm a
bartender and it's fun.
- [Mike] Oh, it's all gone.
How could that have happened?
- [Crow] The young couple
keeps a lot of booze on hand.
- [Mike] Booze heals.
- [Servo] Boy, honey,
It's like we never run out
of things to talk about.
- [Mike] And
there's your chaser.
- [Crow] '50s entertaining
at its most sophisticated.
- [Servo] Back when America
was on top of the world.
- [Mike] Hey, get a
load of this clear beer,
you had this yet?
- Barney, you
should try marriage.
It would do wonders for you.
- [Servo] Just try it.
- [Crow] My answer
is yes, Martin, yes!
- [Narrator] Barney and Martin
had been bachelor
buddies for years.
- [Mike] But is it love?
- [Narrator] And now that
Martin was settling down
to marriage they were
slowly drifting apart.
Barney, naturally, was still
dating all the girls in town.
- [Crow] Naturally.
- And couldn't understand
why Brett and Martin
didn't pal around with
him more than they did.
- [Mike] They hate cops.
- [Narrator] He couldn't
comprehend that married life
brought with it not only
new problems and duties,
but the necessary togetherness--
- [Crow] What's the
narrator talking about?
- [Mike] He's way off script.
- [Crow] He's a renegade
narrator on the loose!
- [Servo] Boy, let me
tell you, he's nuts,
but he never plays
by anybody's rules!
- [Crow] But he gets results!
- [Servo] You wanna
get back to the script?
- [Narrator] Since time began,
this change in relationship
has probably happened
to all buddies in
similar circumstances.
Life has its way of
making boys grow up.
And with marriage,
Martin's time had come.
His life was now Brett, a life
that he thoroughly enjoyed.
- [Mike] Let's watch
them enjoy each other.
- [Servo] So, are you guys
in the mood for Italian or...
I guess not.
- [Crow] Well, I, uh,
I got all the girls in
town waiting for me, so.
- [Mike] Mm, Barney
don't go, mm, mm, mm.
- [Servo] The other guards
don't understand you
like I do, spaceship.
Oh, shh, more later.
- [Crow] I can't resist, you
show the monster a mirror.
He goes nuts.
- [Mike] I want that guy
to get partially eaten
and then spat out.
- [Crow] Aren't you
glad you use dial?
- [Servo] Eh, not that great.
Not like I thought it would be.
Star man.
- [Mike] Oh no, the
thing is going for fluey
and the do-hickey's
going like the deal.
- [Servo] Huh, you
know, it's a federal law
to keep your monster
in a car seat.
- Bye, honey.
- [Mike] I'll make
it home from here.
- [Narrator] The next morning,
Betty Johnson, as usual,
(riffers laughing)
blew a goodbye kiss
to her husband, but
for the last time.
- [Crow] Once a
homecoming queen, always
a homecoming queen.
- [Mike] It's Bess Meyerson.
- [Servo] It's not
really a tent dress.
It's actually a tent.
(baby crying)
- [Crow] Did I have a baby
while I was waving goodbye?
(riffers cooing
and baby talking)
- [Crow] Gimme 10, soldier.
(baby crying)
Well how's my
little boat anchor?
- [Servo] It'll be really
interesting dealing
with this crap for
the rest of my life.
(baby crying)
- Poor baby, let mommy
take your temperature.
- [Crow] No, now get lost.
- [Servo] Uh, I don't
think I want to watch
what's about to happen here.
Uh uh, no way.
- Stop right there.
- Please stop.
- Don't, oh.
- Oh no.
- [Crow] Wait, wait, you're
gonna put that where?
I'm not sick, I'm fine,
look, I'm feeling better!
- Thunk.
- Oh ho ho,
you'll pay for this.
- [Servo] Maybe it's my hair
that's setting him off, hm.
- [Crow] Well, at least we're
not hearing Bruce Willis
make snide comments.
- True, true.
- [Mike] The first
director to realize
the dramatic potential
of a rectal thermometer.
- [Servo] Hm, a little dirty,
might want to consider
flushing the system.
(baby crying)
(soft music)
- Poor baby, you'll
feel better soon.
- [Mike] How about picking
him up or feeding him?
- [Servo] Well, that's done,
now I have the
whole day to myself.
(humming)
- [Crow] Well, my love
deprivation experiment
is going well.
- [Mike] Gee, such a bright
and cheery baby room, huh?
(Servo imitating the soft music)
(new wave music)
- [Servo] Oh, daddy's
home, heh heh.
- [Mike] Man, it's hot in here.
- [Crow] Hey Phil,
which way you goin'?
- [Servo] Everybody
in line back there?
- [Mike] At Moe's Carpets we're
cleaning out our inventory.
- [Crow] It's a
chapel length veil.
(melancholy music)
- [Mike] Meanwhile,
in a Kurosawa film.
(Servo whistling to music)
- [Crow] Well, here's
another really satisfying
part of my day.
- [Servo] Hanging laundry,
maybe I should just hang myself.
- [Mike] Aren't you
supposed to wash 'em first?
- [Crow] Eh, you can leave
babies alone for awhile.
They're usually okay.
- [Servo] So, now
it's trying to become
a taught domestic drama, eh?
(wind blowing)
- [Mike] They're just
downwind from Los Alamos.
- [Servo] Ha, I guess.
- [Crow] Ignore it, ignore
it, just keep hanging clothes,
has nothing to do
with your life.
- [Servo] Oh gack, she had
that pinned to her tongue.
- [Mike] What?
Is that a less dreary
existence I see out there?
- [Crow] I'm in
the hydrangea bush.
- [Servo] Wow, now this is a
very interesting situation,
yes it's...
- [Mike] The bushes mock me.
- [Servo] Hm, a lot
of aphids this year.
- Big ones, mean.
- Wow!
(music intensifies)
- [Crow] Hey, those
are power lines.
- [Servo] Bzz, zzt.
Oh, it's a clothes encounter
of the third kind! (laughs)
- [Crow] Boo.
- [Mike] I got to
get more colors.
- [Crow] When Tom Wolfe's
wife does the laundry.
- [Servo] Maybe if I just
zip by she won't notice me.
- [Mike] Hi, gate was
open, just let myself in.
- [Crow] Can I
borrow some Downy?
(Servo imitates music)
- [Servo] Okay, come on over.
Just don't take your shirt off.
- [Mike] Oh, I hate this
town, take me with you.
- [Crow] Hahaha, Jerry, no!
- [Servo] Can I get
some service here!
(baby crying)
- [Mike] The poignant,
laundry shot.
(Servo burping)
- [Crow] Tell me more
secrets little rocket French.
Shh, shh, shut up.
- [Mike] Wow, the
monster's dryer!
(machine whirring)
- [Servo] Turn it off,
you're flooding it.
- [Crow] Oh, the kid's have
to have every appliance
in the house on.
- [Mike] Maybe the
narrator got eaten.
- [Servo] How many shots
of gauges do you need
in any one movie?
- [Mike] Never have enough.
- [Crow] Duh, I shoulda gone
to DeVry instead of Harvard.
What's this do?
- [Mike] Take this!
(machine beeping and whirring)
- [Servo] What the
hell am I doin' anyway?
- [Crow] I'll just adjust this
so I can watch my stories.
(Servo imitating machine)
- [Mike] There that's
it, you killed it.
- [Servo] Okay kids, please
disembark to the right
and then follow the exit signs.
(light-hearted music)
(Servo whistling Edvard
Grieg's "Morning Song")
- [Crow] Ah, that's a keeper.
- [Servo] Meanwhile, Opie
and his therapist go fishing.
- [Mike] Son, you
and I should really
check out the
village folk scene.
- Grandpa, can I go for a walk?
- All right, but stay close by.
- [Crow] Hey, he's
a matryoshka doll,
there's six more of
him inside! (laughs)
- [Servo] Let's see,
we'll put this here,
no, no, over there,
there that's good.
- [Mike] They have a
really good strategy
of not alerting anyone.
(Servo imitating
light hearted music)
- [Crow] Grandpa's psychosis
is ruining this trip.
(music intensifies)
- [Servo] Seems like
he's in a good mood now.
- [Mike] He's part of the
really big brother program.
- [Servo] Did I just hear a
monster licking at its lips?
(light brass music)
- [Crow] Wow, cannabis.
(Servo singing along with music)
- [Mike] Hm, guess the monster
isn't as big as we thought.
(light brass music)
- [Servo] Ah yes, the
beautiful lizard quartet.
- [Crow] Oh please, I haven't
eaten anything in days.
- [Mike] Cruelty
to small animals
is one of little
Bobby's few outlets.
(music intensifies)
- [Servo] Go tell
Aunt Rhody, oh, hmm?
Tell Aunt, hmm?
- [Crow] Bobby!
While you're up there
grab me a porterhouse too.
- [Mike] He's abdominal riffing.
- Bobby?
- [Servo] And a baked potato.
- And a cake too.
Some Yoo-hoo.
- [Crow] Don't make
me stand up, Bobby!
You know I can't.
- [Mike] Let's see,
I'll put it right here,
and right there.
(light brass music)
- [Crow] This is a portrayal
of deep clinical depression.
- [Servo] Suddenly
it's wild strawberries.
- [Mike] Let's see,
stick, sharpen, Grandpa!
(music intensifies)
- [Crow] Do I smell bacon?
(light hearted music)
(Crow laughing)
- [Servo] Bobby has often
observed his parents at night.
- [Mike] Bobby doesn't
have a lot of friends.
- [Crow] Uh oh,
here comes the most challenging
scene in this movie.
- Bobby!
- [Servo] I'm the
pirate king, huzzah!
- [Crow] Euell Gibbons has got
to cut back on the pine nuts.
- Bobby!
- [Mike] Wow, Bobby
really does not want
to go fishing anymore.
(music intensifies)
- [Servo] He has a manic
interest in nature.
- [Crow] The whole world
is this guy's salad bar.
- [Mike] When Bobby's
hopelessly inbred synapses
slowly begin to fire.
- [Servo] Maury Firestein:
kosher game warden.
- Bobby!
Bobby!
- [Mike] Oh wait,
his name's not Bobby.
Steve! Steve!
- [Crow] You know, making
Allan Sherman an action hero
was not a great idea.
- Bobby.
- [Servo] Bobby,
Bobby,
- [Servo] (laughs)
Bobby shed his antlers.
(Crow laughing)
- Kill kill kill...
- Bobby.
- [Crow] Go go go go...
- Kill kill kill kill...
- [Mike] Whoa, can always
make room for this guy.
- Bobby!
- [Mike] Have you seen Bobby?
Oh, no, probably not.
- [Crow] (chuckles) No, no,
trust me, I'm all gristle!
- [Servo] I taste gamey,
believe me, don't, don't please!
- [Mike] Ironically,
now the fish are biting.
- [Servo] Hey, he's
makin' his own broth.
- [Servo] Let the
current take you away.
Swim!
(Grandpa yelping)
- [Servo] Bobby.
- Help! (yelping)
- [Mike] And the world
has one less Santa.
- [Crow] Meanwhile,
in second hour bio.
- [Narrator] Within 48 hours,
Dr. Bradford had closely
examined the creature
and the space ship.
- [Servo] I've closely
examined the creature.
- [Narrator] And reached
a number of conclusions.
He was sure the creature
had come from beyond
our solar system
because it adapted to our
environment so quickly
and no planet or
dead star near us
has conditions
similar to the Earth.
- [Servo] It was a half
cocked theory, but.
- [Narrator] Of
special interest to him
was the hull of the ship.
- [Servo] The hull of the ship.
- [Narrator] It was
composed of an alloy
unlike anything human
science had ever encountered.
- [Crow] Not buying it.
- [Narrator] The doctor
had run a number of tests
on the metal,
- [Mike] Look up, there's
Phylis's daughter.
- [Narrator] Molecular
structure remained a mystery,
because there was no food
onboard, Bradford presumed
the creature had been in a
state of suspended animation,
particularly because it had
survived the trials of re-entry
and impact without
apparent harm.
So far, he had no success
in communicating with it,
but he had not yet
exhausted all possibilities.
- [Mike] Like candy
and stockings.
- [Narrator] On a
more subjective basis,
He had the curious feeling
that the creature did not want
to communicate with him.
- [Crow] He just wanted to eat.
- [Narrator] Such a
confession on the part
of this eminent
scientist made Martin
feel quite apprehensive.
- [Mike] And dumb.
- [Servo] Then a
cool front moved in,
a low pressure
area out of Canada.
(new wave music)
- Mike, I think it's
time we blew the lid off
"Love, American Style."
- Gypsy, I think you're right.
Hit it, Cambot.
(all singing)
- Mr. Martinson, please!
- But I just want
to dictate to you.
(all singing)
- (laughs) Well, I'm finally
gonna propose to Debbie.
- That's great,
let's see the ring.
Oh no, the ring is stuck.
- I guess we'll
have to get married.
(both laughing)
(all singing)
- But I thought that--
- Well, I thought
that you were--
- This has all been a
big misunderstanding.
- I love you.
(all singing)
- So, take that "Love,
American Style!"
- Now I hope they have the
sense to take it off the air
and the courage to
show this parody.
- And they say there's
no hard hitting satire
on television anymore.
- I dare 'em to show it.
(alarm buzzing)
(everyone yelling at once)
(space ship ambience)
(doors opening)
- [Crow] Ah, ha ha ha.
- [Mike] Come, see the monster,
don't you ever miss it.
- [Narrator] While
on a routine call
to pickup instructions
from Colonel Caldwell
Martin received an urgent
message from Barney.
- [Servo] I love you...
- Barney was at Willow Creek.
He had responded to a phone call
from a frantic Mrs. Brown.
- [Crow] She's got
a lovely daughter.
- [Narrator] Her husband and
grandson had gone fishing
and were long overdue.
- [Servo] I'm in love.
- Barney was instructed to
organize a search party locally
and to report the
results to Martin.
- [Mike] And to organize
a discussion group.
- [Narrator] Because of
security regulations,
he was not to come near
the area of the spacecraft.
- [Crow] Or anybody's area.
- [Narrator] Martin said
he would join Barney later,
if he could.
- [Mike] And watch him and
his wife make kissy face.
- [Servo] They should put
a door on the outhouse.
- [Crow] I gotta
quit doing this.
I can't control it anymore.
Oh, I'm a sick man.
- [Mike] Angel Sheriff,
this fall on NBC.
- [Narrator] Acting on a hunch,
Martin decided to
see for himself
if the monster was still there.
It was.
- [Servo] Case closed.
- [Narrator] Bradford
had installed TV cameras
inside the spaceship
and was testing the creature's
reactions to sound, light,
electricity, color,
and air pressure.
- [Crow] And the
Red Skelton show.
- [Narrator] When Martin
asked him if he had any luck
in communicating with the beast,
- He hit him.
- Bradford confessed
that he hadn't,
but what would try again when
certain data was returned
to him from computer processing.
- [Servo] You like me Bradford?
- [Narrator] It was at
this time that Bradford
came up with a
frightening theory.
Namely that the creature might
be a product of engineering.
The same engineering
that built the spaceship.
- [Crow] And dome homes.
- [Narrator] What he didn't
understand was why some form
of communication had not
been built into the creature.
- [Mike] Martin was
out of his depth now.
- [Narrator] Martin asked
him if this weren't something
to worry about,
Bradford said no.
- [Crow] Don't hit please.
- [Narrator] Probably
his own failing
at not being able to
establish communication.
- [Servo] I'm just
paraphrasing here.
- [Narrator] Seemed to Martin
that if Bradford's
theory were correct,
humanity might be
in grave danger.
- [Mike] From a
Hoover floor model.
- [Narrator] Bradford
dismissed Martin's fears
by pointing out that the
creature was not exhibiting
any signs of violence.
- [Crow] Oh, aside
from eating people.
- [Narrator] Besides, it was
firmly secured by the harness.
That afternoon at Moncrief Park,
a group of neighbors got
together for a hootenanny.
- [Servo] Hoot, hoot, hootyhoo!
- [Mike] And Maria taught the
von Trapp children to sing.
♪ Still I am happy ♪
- [Servo] Trini Lopez puts
on an impromptu performance.
♪ In fact I am glad ♪
- [Mike] This is my
favorite part, listen.
- [Crow] There's only one
stage of grief in this town
and it's acceptance.
♪ She left me alone ♪
♪ And could not marry me ♪
- [Crow] I thought Dave
van Ronk was gonna be here.
- [Mike] This
place is a rip-off.
- [Servo] Come on
Evelyn, let's blow.
- [Mike] Send help!
- [Crow] I admire
their willpower.
♪ But I'll still think of her ♪
- [Servo] Now what a
lovely spot to get killed.
- [Crow] Oh no, the
monster did a doo doo!
- [Servo] Wow!
(melancholy music)
- [Mike] (giggling) These
hootenannies just get me going.
I'm in love, Jim.
- [Servo] Ah, the young
Peter Graves chronicles.
- What is it?
- [Crow] Just our
impending death.
(music intensifies)
- [Mike] Oh no,
they've wandered onto
a federal monster reserve.
- [Servo] Make the
leaves go away.
- [Crow] Oh no, they're
about to be attacked
by a point of view shot!
- [Mike] Uh, no thanks,
we don't want any carpet.
Thank you.
- [Servo] We'll wait
here while you kill us.
- [Mike] Watch the hair.
- [Servo] Making out kills.
- [Crow] Who dare
ruin my folk fest?
- [Mike] El Kabong will kill it.
- You stay there.
Stay calm.
(Servo laughing)
(Crow laughing)
- [Crow] Ah, someone is finally
standing up to the monster.
- [Servo] Only Tom
Paxton can save us now.
- [Mike] Finally putting
his guitar to good use!
- [Crow] Have the army
send in bass and drums.
- [Servo] Ah, years later, Pete
Townsend would perfect this.
(riffers laughing)
- [Mike] Did anyone in the
'50s ever think of running?
- [Servo] Oh, now this
is outright gluttony.
- [Crow] He's depressed
so he just goes out
and eats some campers.
(woman screaming)
- [Servo] Like a giant
pothole, isn't he?
(intense music)
- [Mike] Today, the
music world mourned
the guy who owned this guitar.
- [Narrator] In response
to a multiple missing
persons report,
Martin and Barney
searched the countryside
for the group of picnickers.
- [Servo] I can fix it.
- [Narrator] The only
trace they found of them
was the remains of a
guitar one of them carried.
- [Crow] And some potato salad.
- [Narrator] This wholesale
disappearance of a large
group of people coupled with
earlier missing persons reports
led Martin to only
one conclusion.
- [Servo] Folk is dead.
- [Narrator] There must
be another monster.
And it was on the loose.
- [Mike] The filmmakers
went back to this building
every time they needed a shot.
- [Servo] Yes, mother, yes.
- [Narrator] The colonel
listened to Martin's theory
and after consulting
with Bradford
decided to call Washington.
He was told to follow
his own good judgment--
- [Servo] Uh oh.
- [Narrator] But
under no circumstances
was he to alarm the populace.
The colonel decided to
organize a countywide search
- [Mike] And bake sale.
- [Narrator] Martin's assignment
was to search the north
end of the county.
- [Servo] Mm,
you know, he needs
to walk faster
to maintain an
adequate heart rate
and burn off all those
calories from those people.
- [Crow] His wife
on the other hand,
can eat anything and
not worry about it.
- [Mike] I hate her.
- [Servo] You know
what'd work for him now?
Kind of a low rise pump rather
than those Birkenstocks.
- [Mike] Oh.
I can't believe it,
I'm hungry again!
- [Narrator] While
Martin and Brett
were engaged by the search,
the monster was moving toward
the community dance hall.
- [Crow] Where a close knit
community mourns its dead.
- [Servo] Well, I
assume the authorities
aren't keeping anything from
me, so let's dance! (giggling)
(swing music)
- [Mike] Yeah, here's my torso.
- [Servo] Torso, here's
your torso, look at torso.
- [Mike] Just sing my torso.
- [Servo] Sing her
torso, look at torso.
- [Crow] Timothy Leary and
Estelle Parsons get down.
- [Servo] Woo!
Yeah, I'm surprised we
got this good a turnout
with everyone
being dead and all!
- [Mike] You know,
everyone was 40 back then.
- [Crow] Boy, these Huey
Long fundraisers are great.
- [Servo] Apparently the monster
ate the decorating
committee, hoo!
- [Mike] It's just a good
thing drugs came along.
- [Servo] I'll say.
- [Crow] This town desperately
needs a leather bar.
- [Mike] Even a dairy bar.
- [Servo] The mid afternoon
dance was a big success.
(swing music)
(Crow imitating music)
- [Mike] You can see why the
British invasion so easy.
(Crow imitating music
and Jerry Lewis)
- [Mike] There is just
plain no need for sex.
- [Crow] We'll all be just
fine without it, dear.
- [Mike] That's
right, you tell 'em.
- [Servo] This dance is a
tribute to the treble clef.
- [Mike] You know, even the
AV club laughs at these guys.
- [Crow] They dance to
forget their desperation.
- [Servo] If my deepest darkest
despair had choreography,
this would be it.
- [Mike] Sponsored by Thom McAn.
- [Crow] Hey, no street
shoes on the gym floor!
- [Mike] Your parents
before you were born.
(Servo laughs)
- [Crow] Hey, there's
a hair on the...
Hey, there's a hair on
the thing, would you?
Thank you.
- [Servo] And as ever,
the Baptists remain
on the sidelines.
- [Crow] This was
the unsuccessful
pilot for Soul Train.
- [Mike] Well, I can see
why they need a rest.
- [Servo] Yeah, wow,
pshew, tell them.
- [Crow] Hey, where'd
the tablecloth go?
- [Mike] (gasps)
Shh, don't bother it.
They're so beautiful
in the wild.
- [Crow] Yes.
I need to find somebody who
is rich in antioxidants.
- [Mike] Must get to dance
before punch runs out!
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] Will the
monster marry Susan,
and what about their baby?
Tune in tomorrow and find out.
- [Crow] Okay, one more
dance, but it'll cost you.
- [Mike] Oh good, they're
playing my request.
- [Crow] Now girls, I
can't marry both of you.
(swing music)
- [Servo] One more drink
and he'll be attractive.
- [Mike] Oh, I'm
embarrassed for them.
- [Servo] I know
she's a divorcee.
(Crow imitating squeaking shoes)
- [Crow] And I hope I didn't
overdress for this thing.
- [Mike] Ah, well finally,
here comes someone with rhythm!
(swing music)
Rump, rump, rump, rump,
rumpity, rump, rump,
rump, rump, rump, rump,
rump, rump, rump.
Plenty of rump.
- [Servo] Oh, it's
Marty on his date.
- [Mike] Here comes
some juicy rump,
a little more rump here,
a little more rump there.
- [Crow] Yee haa, yee haa.
- [Servo] Stood up by a monster.
Oh sure, I'll meet
you here. (grumbling)
Monsters, all alike.
- To hell with it!
- [Crow] This is not jazz!
- Come on, Rita.
I've had enough of that guy.
- [Mike] Sorry, folks,
should have told you
about the subplot.
Even caught me, the
narrator, off guard.
- [Servo] Hey, David Carradine!
- [Mike] Yeah!
- [Servo] Okay, hi!
Dave.
- [Crow] Oh, he's
been a bull drunk
and now suddenly
he surreptitious.
- [Mike] Oh, his date is
so humiliated right now!
- [Servo] Uh, Susan, I
can't seem to stop, help.
Ow.
(monster screeching)
- [Crow] I gotta get in
there, it sounds so hot!
- [Mike] Hope I
didn't miss the part
where they throw the bouquet.
(monster roaring)
- [Servo] Everybody
okay back there?
- [Crow] Why didn't
I park closer?
(swing music)
- [Mike] Hey, even
the chemistry teacher
can shake his booty!
- [Servo] It's Oskar
Schindler and the Boston Pops.
- [Crow] It's an
all chaperone dance.
- [Mike] I've got
the music in me.
- [Servo] Come on, take
me to funky town. (laughs)
- [Crow] Mm, never eaten
a whole prom before.
- [Mike] But Patty
likes to rock and roll,
the hot dog makes
her lose control.
- [Servo] Woo!
(swing music)
- [Servo] Wow, her hinder,
it's outta control!
- [Crow] It's got
a mind of its own!
- [Mike] I don't
blame him for ogling.
- [Servo] What are
you lookin' at?
- [Crow] Ah, the Dts!
Get these bugs off me!
Oh wait, I'm a bug.
(Servo making jiggling sound)
(Mike laughing)
- [Mike] He's a maniac
and he's dancing like
he's never danced before.
- [Servo] Man, if I
don't score tonight...
(monster roaring)
(swing music)
(woman screams)
- [Mike] I know, I
know, it's a cheap suit,
but it's all I had.
(woman screaming)
- [Servo] Why is
everybody lookin' at me?
- My God, what is it?
(riffers laughing)
- [Crow] Uh, Mr. Monster,
we need to stamp your hand.
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] Music's better.
- [Mike] What the?
- [Servo] What?
Wow.
- [Mike] Hey, enough
with the subplot,
I'm tryin' to attack you guys!
- [Crow] Keanu Reeves has
it out with Ed Begley Jr.
- [Servo] Oo.
What? (laughs)
What a disgusting race.
To think I've been
eatin' these clowns!
(dramatic music)
(monster roaring)
- [Crow] Uh, anybody
sittin' here?
- [Mike] Everybody leave in
a slow, leisurely manner.
- [Servo] Anybody wanna dance?
Come on.
- [Crow] Hey, everybody
look at my tracheotomy!
Wait, I'll do the
cigarette trick.
- [Mike] What's the panic?
He's on cleanup committee.
- [Servo] 'Scuse me, is this
the way to the cafeteria?
- [Crow] It's so hard to
be the new kid in school.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Are you sure
you're not looking
for the Feinberg wedding, sir?
- [Crow] Just making my
way to the buffet, folks.
- [Mike] You guys
goin' to Todd's?
I'll meet ya there.
I'll catch up.
(monster roaring)
- [Servo] Sheer energy. (laughs)
- [Crow] Please, I'm not
ready for an open mouth kiss!
- [Mike] Hey, it's actually
pretty cool in here!
- [Servo] Meanwhile, in
a totally different movie
in a completely
unrelated high school.
- [Mike] What the Sam Scratch?
- [Crow] Fight, fight.
Doesn't anyone eat anymore?
(monster screeching)
(riffers imitating monster)
- [Mike] I'm just gonna sit
in with the band for a few.
(imitating monster)
- [Servo] Oh no, oh
God, oh hi, Debbie!
(laughs) Good to see ya!
- [Crow] How are they
gonna explain this
in the Angel County Herald?
- [Mike] Oh, I'm done.
I've gotta push myself
away from the table.
- [Servo] I know what happens.
Now pig's blood is gonna
be dumped on his head.
- [Crow] Eh, could I see
a dessert menu, please?
- [Mike] Be kinda ironic
if he had a tapeworm, huh?
(dramatic music)
- [Servo] Where's Frederick,
our usual maitre d?
- [Crow] Go ahead, honey,
he's bein' friendly!
- [Mike] Now he's just
gulping his food, this is...
- [Servo] I think this is
kind of a weird little turn-on
for the director.
- [Mike] Oh hi,
Joann, scooch over.
- [Crow] I love
you, you big lug!
- [Servo] Thank you,
thank you very much.
Thank you, thank you.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] What's great
about this monster is that
he can pretty much be his
own sleeping accommodations.
- [Crow] Hey, knock
it off in there!
Settle down!
You're kickin' my...
- [Servo] Oh no, he's choking!
Someone give him the
Heimlich maneuver!
(monster screeching)
- [Mike] He died with
his bowling shoes on.
- [Crow] Well, hello, ladies!
- [Mike] Monsters
think we're weird
'cause we chew our food.
(Servo burps)
- [Crow] You know, this
monster was up for a part
in Naked Lunch.
- [Mike] Oh, really?
- [Servo] I need some
juice or something.
Man, people are salty.
(new wave music)
- [Crow] Chris Isaak!
- [Servo] Oh, break time, honey.
- [Narrator] While
Martin and Brett
were taking a break
from the search,
a call came through which
confirmed Martin's theory.
- [Mike] This movie sucks.
- [Narrator] Colonel
Caldwell told them
of the monster's attack
at the dance hall
- [Servo] In
graphic terminology.
- [Narrator] His
troops now had orders
to destroy the monster
and he asked for
Martin's assistance.
- [Crow] Martin declined.
- [Narrator] Martin said
he would join the colonel
as quickly as possible.
- [Mike] Were in not
for his trick knee.
- John!
- Marsha!
- Marsha?
- [Mike] Say what you
will about this planet,
they throw great dances.
- [Crow] You know
what I could use?
A mint, blech.
- [Servo] Oh, they clear
cut a virgin forest
so's people could make out.
Nummy.
- [Narrator] The monster next
appeared in lover's lane.
- [Mike] To a sold out crowd!
- [Narrator] Anyone who
experienced that catastrophe
and survived would
never go there again.
- [Servo] Those who did not
survive such a catastrophe
also would not go there again.
- [Crow] Okay, now this time
I'm gonna give you guys
a head start, all right?
- [Mike] No, trees
aren't that great
after you've had people.
- [Servo] (grunting) What?
Lover's lane, eight miles!
Oh man, aw!
- [Crow] Oh, he's
a little dizzy.
He ate too much of
his Halloween people.
(ominous music)
- [Mike] And just who am I
supposed to make out with?
- [Servo] Aw.
- [Crow] Oh no, in
the heart of the beast
puppet theater is here!
- [Servo] I'll just sneak up
and surprise them. (giggles)
Tomorrow.
(monster screeching)
- [Servo] Honey, I think
we've got creeping terror.
- [Crow] Not in front
of the monster, dear.
- [Mike] (gasps) Marisa Tomei!
(monster roaring)
- [Servo] This is too easy!
Num, num, num, num, num,
num, num, num, num, num.
- [Crow] Uh, Mike?
(laughs nervously)
- [Mike] Well, you see, when
a monster and a small car
love each other very much...
- [Crow] Wow!
- [Servo] People melt in
your mouth, not in your car.
- [Crow] He's mistaken the
car for a lady monster!
Hoo!
- Oh, wow!
- [Mike] Why doesn't
the monster take the car
so he can get his
work done faster?
- [Servo] Well, that was a
new twist on an old trick, eh?
- [Crow] Ah, well,
that was good.
Now for the people in the
Oldsmobile. (smacks lips)
- [Mike] And the
Beta Kappa Chi float
wins the homecoming parade!
- [Servo] Oh, he always
comes to lover's lane alone.
(monster screeching)
- [Mike] Well, if
that don't beat all.
- [Crow] Ah, I wouldn't
have eaten you anyway.
(monster screeching)
- [Servo] Oh, should I?
I've eaten so much already.
Well, Thanksgiving
only comes once a year.
- [Mike] Creeping part is apt,
but the terror part,
it's just not happening.
(ominous music)
(Servo singing with music)
- [Crow] Heh heh, he's doing
his Walter Brennan impression!
Heh heh.
- Dagnabit.
- [Mike] Get out of the way.
I want to see the smoochers.
- [Servo] He's definitely
a people person.
- [Crow] Thanks, I'll
return it with a full tank.
- [Mike] An official jalopy.
- [Servo] Like to see your
license registration, please.
(imitating monster)
- [Mike] Hey, can I get a lift?
I gotta doctor's appointment.
- [Crow] I'm a hideous growth
and I gotta have me removed!
- [Mike] Woo, Bulls won!
- [Crow] Woo, Bulls!
- [Servo] Huh, well.
- God!
- [Crow] That was the
last straw for that guy.
(riffers laughing)
- [Mike] Just tryin' to
give him a push start.
- [Servo] You got
it in gear, right?
(monster screeching)
- [Crow] Jackson
Pollock disapproves.
- [Servo] Well, he's tenacious,
you gotta give him that.
- [Mike] Ah, it looks like
you're gonna need some
transmission work.
- [Crow] Oh dear, lift
with your legs now.
- [Servo] Unsafe at any speed.
Yuck!
- [Mike] Ah.
Those kids with their
chinos and ah...
- [Crow] Hope he didn't pay
a lot for that detailing job.
- [Servo] That monster'd
make a really cool fort.
(monster roaring)
Big.
- [Mike] Ah, comfort food.
- [Crow] I like
the meaty filling!
- [Servo] But if
they're not dead,
they can't just crawl into
his mouth like the others.
- [Mike] Problem.
Oh, great date, Steve.
- [Crow] Wait a
minute, here I come.
(laughs) Skirt got caught.
- [Mike] Can't get this
vending machine to work.
Just want a Clark bar!
- [Servo] Oh, I hate this.
I can see 'em, but
I can't get to 'em!
- [Crow] Oh, my three
stomachs are growling, oh!
- [Mike] It's really more
trouble than it's worth.
Hey, give it up!
- [Servo] Jesus,
like a Brazil nut,
there's no gettin' into it!
- [Crow] Well, they're not
gonna be as fresh as I like 'em,
but what the hey?
(Servo imitating monster)
- [Mike] He's just not as
nimble as he used to be.
I think he's put on some
weight or something.
- [Servo] Coochie
coochie brooha!
- [Mike] Please
God, I'm only 17.
- [Servo] Yuck.
- [Crow] Okay, I'm just
gonna have these two
then first thing Monday
morning, I'm going on that diet.
- [Servo] You know,
ever since the divorce,
he's learned how to
cook for himself.
- [Mike] Oh, he likes
it fresh out of the can.
- [Crow] Jeez, you know, now
I'm not even that hungry.
- [Servo] He's just
playing taking advantage
of the all-you-can-eat
buffet on Earth.
(monster screeching)
- [Mike] Ricky, Gary, hi.
You guys got eaten, too?
- [Servo] Yeah. (laughs)
- [Mike] Oh, come on
in here, all right.
- [Crow] Mr. Monster, you've
got some leg on your face!
(laughs)
- [Servo] Check this
out. (sings the can-can)
(laughs)
- [Mike] Wow, the
monster's got great gams.
- [Servo] (whistles) Okay.
(chomping)
Ah, ah, you all
comfortable in there?
- [Mike] Yes, thank
you, Mr. Monster.
- [Servo] (chuckles)
Yeah, okay, kids.
- [Mike] Time to undo my pants
and go watch the football game.
- [Crow] You know, humans
really stick to my dental work.
- [Servo] And I bet his
breath really stinks.
- [Crow] Especially after
he eats French people!
(Crow and Servo laughing)
- [Mike] What is with you
and the French people?
- [Servo] Oh, it's
funny. (laughs)
- [Mike] Monster's
gotta be full by now.
- [Crow] I'm sorry, I
shouldn't have said that.
(ominous music)
(spaceship ambience)
(door shutting)
- Wow.
- Hey guys, finally got
my stereo system set up.
- It looks pretty substantial,
Mike, what kind is it?
- Oh, it's nothin' much.
Got the Nakamichi
CD 1000 transport
fiber linked to the PS
Audio 20 bit DA converter.
Course that goes to my
Bryston straight line preamp
out to the Carver
400 watt mono blocks
and over the DCM
time window sevens.
- Yeah, sounds great, Mike.
As for me, I've got one of
them Gold Star book shelf jobs.
- Yeah, a boombox is
enough for me, Mike.
- You disgust me.
- Huh?
- Come on, guys!
Haven't you ever
heard a good system?
Get into the sweet spot here.
Now listen to this, come on.
As the kids say, this
is gonna blow your mind.
(swing music from the movie)
- Mike, that's the music
from "The Creeping Terror"!
- Yeah.
- Sounds pretty lame, Mike.
- Oh come on, listen to the
definition, the imaging.
There's plenty of air
around the instruments.
Here, let me replay this part.
(music rewinding)
Replay that, listen
to that, huh?
(swing music)
- Huh, yeah, neat.
Well, you know, Mike,
I think we're gonna listen
to it from over here, right.
- Yeah, yeah, oh look at,
there's the sweet spot!
Over here!
- Hey!
Ah, fine, who needs ya?
(swing music)
(equalization changes)
- Hey, you wanna catch
that button, Crow?
- [Mike] That was
great, thank you.
- [Servo] Hey, meals on wheels.
- [Mike] Now to make
my speedy getaway.
- [Narrator] It was almost an
hour before Caldwell learned
of the monster's
devastating new attack.
Colonel Caldwell wasted no time
ordering his men into action.
- [Crow] Men, action.
(Servo laughing)
- [Narrator] It was at this
point that Bradford interceded.
He demanded that the monster
be taken alive at all costs.
The colonel's protests
about the dead and missing
made no impression on Bradford.
- [Mike] Dead, missing, so what?
- [Narrator] Caldwell
conceded to the point
of assuring Bradford that they
would not destroy the monster
if they could avoid it.
- [Servo] Because
monsters are people too.
(monster screeching)
- [Caldwell] Get on
with it Lieutenant.
- Move it out, men.
- [Crow] Actual dialogue
startled everyone.
(intense music)
(monster screeching)
- [Mike] Yes, I am
handsome, thank you.
- [Servo] God, he is
attractive, isn't he?
- [Crow] We're from the
set of combat, can we help?
- [Servo] Everything he
eats, goes to his hips.
(police siren wailing)
- [Mike] Then Broderick
Crawford arrived.
- [Servo] Well it's cowboy
day down to the precinct.
- [Narrator] When
Martin's party arrived
and offered to help,
the Colonel told
them enough lives
were being endangered.
They were to be part of
the second line of defense
to be used only if necessary.
- [Crow] Also known as dessert.
(monster screeching)
- [Mike] Guys, don't tempt
me, I'm stuffed, please.
(riffers making gun sounds)
(monster screeching)
- [Crow] Well, I guess
one more wouldn't hurt,
come on, get in!
- [Mike] Hey, come on,
I got you, lay down.
- [Crow] Hey, I
see Judy in there.
(Crow laughing)
- [Servo] What?
- [Mike] Apparently just
hoping it would go away,
didn't really work.
- [Servo] He tampered
in God's domain.
- [Crow] The monster's
got corn smut.
(riffers laughing)
- [Servo] Didn't work when
we shot James Beard either.
(gunfire)
- [Mike] The words "nyah
nyah" were clearly heard.
(gunfire)
♪ Here we come ♪
- [Servo] Wait, wait,
you don't understand.
Let me tell you why I
ate your family, jeez.
- [Crow] This is an intervention
for his eating disorder.
(riffers imitating gun sounds)
- [Mike] Look, we have
some Susan Powder tapes
we want you to look at.
(Crow laughing)
- [Crow] The photographer
fell on them.
- [Servo] Pod pile, hep hep hep.
- [Mike] Well golly.
- [Servo] Diaper me,
diaper me please.
- [Crow] What kind of a memorial
do we build to those guys, eh?
- [Narrator] The
sergeant, a shaken man,
returned babbling about
what had happened.
(Servo babbling)
Realizing the whole
danger of the situation,
decided he had only one means
left to stop the monster.
Grenades.
- [Mike] Renee, who's she?
- [Narrator] Now Bradford
made a drastic move,
- [Crow] He gestured.
- [Narrator] Acting
under superior authority,
he forbad Caldwell to
destroy the creature.
- [Mike] He forbad?
- [Narrator] The
Colonel, more concerned
with saving human lives
than advancing science,
told Bradford to go to hell.
- [Servo] Pardon my French.
- Get out of my way!
- [Mike] We're gonna
put some of those
little Vietnamese peppers in
my pocket and let him eat me.
(monster screeching)
- [Mike] Okay baggy, now
you'll meet my creeping terror.
- [Crow] Um, Mr. Monster,
could you spit out
our rifles please?
- [Mike] Hamilton, Joe
Frank, and Reynolds attack.
- [Servo] Come on, come
on, you want a piece of me?
Oh, you do actually.
- [Crow] Oh, he broke a heel!
- [Mike] Guy's wearing
maternity pants.
(monster screeching)
- [Servo] Look at that, huh.
Foiled him with crab grass.
Ooo.
- [Crow] Something sort
of happened, kind of.
- [Mike] Yeah there was a, hmm.
Just tell me, am I
inside the monster?
(riffers making kissing sounds)
- [Crow] Ah, ya fragged
yourself, ya knucklehead!
- [Servo] You were
there and you and you.
- [Mike] T'was Buford
killed the beast.
- [Crow] This has been the
goofiest week of my life.
- [Servo] Huh?
What the?
Hey, this is pleather.
- [Mike] Oh man, he's
goin' through his wallet.
- [Crow] There's $5 in here,
and a pass for
Cheapskate roller rink.
- [Servo] Lookit that, dang
monster's from Radio Shack.
(intense music)
- [Crow] Richard
Kimball, man on the run.
(intense music)
(Servo singing along)
- Whoa-ho-ho!
- Safe!
- [Crow] He slides
like Ron Santo.
- Where's he going
in such a hurry?
- [Servo] Maybe his
beeper went off.
(Servo imitating music)
- Maybe you better follow him.
He may need help.
You go ahead, Martin.
I'll stay with Colonel.
- [Mike] Come along,
special agent sweetheart.
- [Servo] Here on KROL, all
roller rink music, all the time.
(Servo imitating music)
- [Crow] This portion of
our film brought to you
by Ensco windshield wipers.
Ensco wipers, when you're
wet, they wipe you.
- [Mike] Only after
the monster died
did people think of running.
- [Servo] May I dab tenderly
at your forehead, Steve?
(piano and organ music)
- [Mike] Ray Manzarek on organ.
- [Crow] And thus the
chase scene begins.
(Servo and Mike coughing)
- [Servo] So, was this a
silent movie all of a sudden?
(Servo and Crow imitating music)
- [Mike] Jeez, I just sort
of panicked back there.
I don't know what happened.
- [Crow] Here in White Valley.
- [Servo] Hm, just
keeps thinkin'
about those two
scoops of raisins.
- [Crow] Gotta
find a petting zoo.
There are times when a man
needs the touch of a llama.
(police siren wailing)
(Servo imitating music)
- [Mike] Somewhere in Black
Mountain Hills of Dakota
there lived a young boy
named Rocky Raccoon.
- [Servo] Enjoy my
profile, won't you?
- [Crow] Oh no, a nuclear blast!
- [Mike] When the agents
reached the Spahn Ranch,
Manson and his followers
were nowhere to be seen.
(new wave music)
(organ and piano music)
- [Servo] This is Andy
Warhol's, "Driving".
(Crow singing Sanford
and Son theme)
- [Mike] I had to get here.
Not sure what here
is, but I'm here.
- [Crow] Forget the
password, let me in!
(metallic thumping)
- [Mike] I am sleeping!
- [Servo] Jeez, did I
leave the monster on?
- Woo!
- Woah!
- [Crow] Oh, something happened.
- [Servo] I guess.
- [Crow] Oh bad thing burn bad
ow stingy pain ow (spitting)
- Put him out.
- Put me out.
- [Mike] I'd walk a million
miles, for one of your smiles.
- [Servo] Mommy.
- [Narrator] The explosions
loosened the harness
on the monster, and
allowed it to escape.
- [Mike] And so our
tale begins again.
- [Servo] Oh no.
- [Crow] The filmmakers
sadly misread
the demand for a sequel.
(monster screeching)
(man screaming)
- [Servo] Guess he
wanted a Manwich, huh?
Sorry.
- [Crow] Too bad the monster
didn't land in Thailand,
he'd have heartburn by now.
- [Servo] Oh now
with the food jokes.
(monster screeching)
- [Mike] Listen, he sounds
like Screamin' Jay Hawkins.
(Servo imitating monster)
- [Servo] Jeez, would
you just come and get me!
Let's get this over with.
Lyin' here.
(monster screeching)
- [Mike] Oh, look at that,
he's gonna be walkin' soon.
- [Crow] This might be
rather cynical on my part,
but I put it to you that
that is the same monster.
- [Servo] Oh God no.
Oh, it's not possible.
Oh the humanity.
- [Mike] Oh, I have a question.
Uh, you're going to
eat me, aren't you?
- [Crow] No, no this
guy won't be eaten,
'cause the monster
hates Cajun food.
- [Servo] Please.
- [Crow] Blackened, heh-heh.
- [Servo] Blacken you.
- [Mike] I think I
hit on something.
Stay away from his mouth.
Don't crawl inside
of it, that's it!
- [Crow] Hey, a
four leaf clover!
- [Servo] Suddenly he suffers
from a narcolepsy seizure.
(Servo singing)
- [Mike] No, come on
rascal, no, no, not now.
- [Crow] I need to
ask Phil something.
Could you barf him up please?
(police siren wailing)
(man whimpering)
(riffers laughing)
- [Servo] Sorry, he just
darted out in front of me.
- [Mike] Bradford just
squirted all over the place.
- [Servo] Wow.
- [Crow] Here, let me give
you my insurance information.
- [Mike] Oh, hi!
- [Narrator] Martin
tried to help the doctor.
But there was no time.
Bradford told Martin what
he had just confirmed.
- [Crow] I'm dying.
- [Narrator] That these
monsters were highly specialized
test animals.
They were in fact
mobile laboratories
that consumed human beings
in order to analyze
them chemically,
undoubtedly to detect
weaknesses in the human species.
- [Servo] Oh, undoubtedly.
- [Narrator] He told Martin
that the information fed
into a computer
in the spacecraft.
Further, he added, now that
both monsters were dead,
the computer would
activate a transmitter
to send the results
into outer space.
- [Servo] Uh huh.
- [Narrator] Martin
knew what he had to do.
- [Crow] Become a
huge Larry Storch fan.
He'd follow him around the
country, seeking his autograph.
He'd be an expert
on Larry Storch.
Able to answer any question
about Larry Storch.
- [Mike] So if he gets
killed or anything
you want to have
coffee sometime?
- [Narrator] Martin
entered the spaceship.
He heard the transmitter
generator kick on.
- [Servo] Whoa.
- [Crow] Ah jeez,
I should know this,
I went to refrigeration school.
- [Mike] Hey, hey
there's bullets
in the other end of that thing.
- [Servo] It's a closet
Luddite, this guy.
- [Narrator] The super tough
alloys of the spacecraft
were not even dented
by Martin's hammering.
- [Crow] You never loved
me, you never loved me!
- [Mike] Another
frustrated IBM PC user.
- [Servo] Stupid
old machine, stupid.
- [Crow] You can just unplug it.
- [Mike] Spaceships got
a supporting beam there.
- [Crow] Why don't you just
ask the spaceship nicely
to go away?
- [Servo] So, how many of him
do you think it would take
to screw in a light bulb?
- [Crow] All of them.
Hey, Hey, take it easy,
Roger Corman needs to
use this set later.
(intense music)
- [Servo] Finally, the
failure of his wedding night
comes crashing down on him.
- [Mike] Martin's upset because
the thing is transmitting
bad stuff about him.
- [Servo] Jack Nicholson
courteous drivers school.
- [Crow] After his release,
Stacy Koon gets a
job at Cray computer.
- [Mike] You thought
you were off the hook.
You get back here and
take it like a man.
(Servo breathing heavily)
- [Crow] There, what
do you think of that?
- [Servo] I'm sorry, I
didn't mean the lash out.
Please forgive me. (sobbing)
- [Narrator] As the transmitter
stopped, Martin felt sick.
(Mike making puking noises)
Evidently all the information
had been transmitted.
- [Crow] Well, we're dead,
world's over, my fault, sorry.
- [Mike] Hey crispy,
hands off my wife.
- [Narrator] On Martin's return,
he confessed his failure.
- [Mike] Forgive me
Bradford, for I have failed.
- [Narrator] He
slowly asked Bradford
what was in store for humanity?
Bradford was pessimistic,
but implied that maybe
all was not lost.
- [Mike] He had coupons.
- [Narrator] After
all, he told them,
the vastness of the
universe is incredible.
If these monsters had
come from its outer limit,
- [Mike] Makes good sense.
- [Narrator] Their home
might even no longer exist.
Or if they do come again,
perhaps man will have advanced
enough to cope with them
and those who made them.
- [Crow] Or words
to that effect.
- [Narrator] "Only
God knows for sure,"
were Bradford's last words
to anyone on this earth.
- [Servo] Not quite as pithy as,
"Either these
curtains go or I do,"
but still, it was
the best he could do.
- [Crow] Well, should
we eat 'em or bury 'em?
Kidding.
- [Servo] I vote eat.
- [Mike] Eat.
Honey, is anything wrong?
Man, women are so emotional.
- [Crow] What were
you two talkin' about?
- [Servo] Keep
watching the skies!
And watch what you eat!
But eat all you take!
- [Mike] A bird in
the hand is worth, uh.
- [Crow] I've been to
one state fair, a rodeo,
and that's the stupidest
thing I've ever seen!
- The end, end, say the end
- End, end, yes, yes, end
- We're gonna leave anyway
- End, end, end, end, end!
- Ahh!
(space ship ambience)
(doors closing)
(Servo and Crow laughing)
- [Crow] Here I come, Tommy!
- [Servo] Okay, buddy,
slide right down!
- Crow, what in the
world are you doing!
- Hey hey hey!
(Gypsy groaning)
- Ow, right on my head!
- Now come on up here!
- Thanks, Mike.
Oh, I hope you don't
think that was my idea.
- No, I think I know
whose idea it was.
Hey, Tom!
- [Servo] Hey, Mike, see if
ya can get her to swallow you.
It's really neat.
(Crow laughing)
- Oh, this is so embarrassing.
I don't look fat, do I?
- No, Gypsy, you don't look fat,
you're a little lumpy
maybe, but not fat.
- Oh, this is embarrassing.
- [Servo] Come on,
hop in and experience
the allometry canal in action,
it's the ultimate trip.
- Uh, no thanks,
I think I'll pass.
- Okay.
- Uh, so to speak.
Anyway, we got
letters to read here.
- Yes, yes.
- You know, Mike, I, I don't
feel very well all of a sudden.
I think I'm getting
allergic to Tom.
- Yeah, join the club, Gypsy.
- Hey.
- I think I'll go get
a tissue, I think uh--
- Okay.
Crow, ya want to read
some letters here.
- Me?
- Yeah.
- May I?
- Well, you're
the only one here.
- Oh boy, thanks
for choosing me!
- Weren't my first choice, but,
no I'm kidding.
- I know.
- Alright, here we go,
this one is from uh,
put that on still store there,
'cause this is from Jason
of the salt right of fun.
- What the hell does that mean?
- It says it right there.
Jason of the salt right of fun.
And he says, "Superman's a comic
book, not a graphic novel."
- Superman's dead.
- He also says, "PS, the
robot in the picture is 2XL,
and can I be on your show?"
- It's a neat robot, but no,
you can't be on our show.
Sorry.
- No no no no no.
- Sorry, Jason of the
salt right of fun.
- That was weird.
(Mike laughing)
- Now, this next one
is from David Banks.
- Hello, David!
- Hello, Dave!
- That's wild Dave.
- And he says,
"I have found that your show
is one of the best around.
I especially love it
when Crow says 'Kitties!'
when dangerous lions are seen.
Please ask Crow to say
'Kitties' a couple
of times for me."
Crow?
- Oh I don't know, Michael
- A little command performance--
- I just can't indulge
every little fan request!
- A little massage.
- Oh yes, that's it.
Kitties.
(Gypsy violently sneezing)
- Ahhh! (metal slamming)
Woo hoo.
- Well, guess it's back to
you, Dr. Clayton Forrester.
Are you all right?
- Mike, you better
come and look at this.
- [Servo] It burns, it burns.
- Well, until we meet again.
On behalf of Frank and myself,
here's wishing
you whiter whites,
- Whiter whites.
- Brighter brights,
- Brighter brights.
- May all your rinse
cycles be gentle
(Frank moaning)
and may all your troubles
come out in the wash.
(chuckling) Ta ta.
(TV turning off)
(brassy swing music)
(monster screeching)
(woman screaming)
- My god, what is it?